Kinko's. This is Danny. Can I help you?
Kinko复印社. 我是Danny. 我能为您效劳吗?
Sure. Yes we do. All night. Bye.
当然啦. 是的. 我们通宵都开着. 再见.
My my, we are eager to answer the phone tonight.
My my, 今天晚上接电话可真积极呀.
Do you think the owner's going to call?
你以为老板会打电话过来?
Danny, you can relax, man, because he's fast asleep.
Danny, 放松点儿, 伙计, 他这会儿肯定睡得死死的.
Just serving the customer, Nathan.
我只是接待顾客而已, Nathan.
She had questions. I had answers.
她既然有问题要问, 我就回答她啦.
I don't suppose this new work ethic extends to the supply room, does it?
我想你这种崭新的职业道德不会运用到储藏室的工作上去吧?
We need some things.
我们需要一些东西.
No, thanks. I'll man the front desk. Answer the phones.
不, 谢谢. 我就负责前台. 负责接电话.
I guess I should be glad you'll do anything.
我想你能想着做点儿事情我就该很高兴了.
Kinko's. This is Danny. Can I help you?
Kinko复印社. 我是Danny. 我能为您效劳吗?
Hi. No, this is fine.
Hi. 不, 没关系的.
Call me here for those early morning assignments.
那些一大清早的工作你尽管打电话来这儿找我好了.
So, where do I go today?
那么, 我今天去哪儿?
Wait, wait, wait. They want me to dress as a what?
等等, 等等, 等等. 他们要我打扮成一个什么?
What do you mean, a prince?
你说什么, 王子?
Listen, I'm not an actor. I'm a guy in a tuxedo.
我说, 我又不是演员. 我只是身上穿了一件礼服的家伙.
I don't have the costumes to be a prince. Or a king. Or a clown.
我没有扮演王子, 国王, 或者小丑的服装.
Where do I pick them up?
我上哪儿去取?
Downtown. Nine o'clock. Bye.
市中心. 9点钟. 再见.
Tough customer, huh?
难缠的顾客, huh?